欢迎回家 小德怀特
Welcome home, Dwighty boy.
我得说
I gotta say,
你回来真是太好了
it is damn good having you back.
事情必须完成
See, things gotta get done.
我需要一流的手下助我获胜
I need my top guys ‭out in front acing that shit.
谢谢
Thanks.
我听说你死里逃生了
Had yourself a close call, I hear.
我遭到了埋伏
I got ambushed.
中了一枪
I took this.
其他人没能逃走
The rest didn't walk away.
直到
Well, until…
我到了森林 继续前行
I got to the woods, kept going.
我朝山顶寨走去
You know, I headed toward Hilltop.
我想着我们的人
I figured our people would be.
迟早会封锁那片地区
putting up a blockade sooner or later.
干得好
Good job.
但我们解除了封锁
But we pulled the blockade.
得让老鼠玩一会儿
Have to let the mice play a little,
因为
'cause, you know…
我们的人得分清轻重缓急
our people need ‭to get their business in order.
你会看到的
You'll see.
不如你喝杯啤酒
So, why don't you just slug a beer,
穿上最好的背心 下楼去
put on your best vest, and get your ass downstairs,
因为像我所说
'cause like I said…
我们还有事情要做
…we got work.
好好搞
Get 'em good.
溅出来也没关系
It's all right if they spill out.
我要收集起来以备后用
I'm gonna gather up the jackpots for refreshers,
内脏就是内脏
and guts is guts.
深深地搅一搅
Push it in nice and deep.
好东西
That's the stuff.
天啊
Holy damn!
一定会非常棒的
This is gonna be all kinds of awesome.
等山顶寨尝到我们的苦头
Once the Hilltop just feels the tip of what we are packin'…
他们会立马跪下屈服
…they are gonna drop to their knees lickety-split.
是啊 老大
Yes, sir.
听好了
Listen up!
今天的重点是吓唬这些人
Today is about scaring these people.
我们不要打头 皮肉伤即可
We're not going for head shots, just flesh wounds.
伤一些人 让他们活着 变成行尸
Hit a few, leave 'em livin', let 'em turn.
但别杀了他们
But don't kill 'em.
小德
D.
尼根自己开车
Negan's handling his own transport,
你可以跟我坐一辆
so you can ride with me.
我打算侦察一下
Well, I'm gonna scout ahead,
看看前方有没有敌人
see if anything's coming our way.
想得很细致
Well, considerate thought,
但我们有侦察队在侦察 对吧
but we got scouts scouting, right?
比起你来更可牺牲的士兵
Far more expendable soldiers than you,
我不是说你可牺牲 完全不是这意思
which is not to say ‭you're expendable … at all.
听着 跟我坐一辆
Listen, ride with me,
我路上给你讲讲计划
we make sure ‭you're up to speed on the plan.
这是尼根的意思
It's what Negan wants,
我不知道我们为什么还在唠叨
so I don't know why we're still jawing.
他说什么 我们就做什么
He says, we do.
你真美 宝贝
You look beautiful, baby.
《行尸走肉》
来吧 亲爱的
Come here, sweetheart.
对
Yeah.
我
You know, I…
我环顾四周
I look around and…
想到了那些逝去的人
I think about the people that are gone…
和还在这里的人
…and the people that are still here.
这不对
It ain't right.
这也不公平
And it ain't fair.
听着 关于
Look, about…
我在救世堂的所作所为
what I did at Sanctuary,
试图迅速地结束一切…
trying to end it real quick…
我只是想做个了结
I just wanted it done.
我不想再给他们一个机会
I didn't want ‭to give them another chance,
不能再给了
not again.
我当时根本没在乎有谁在那里
And I didn't care who was there.
我不知道这样是不是对的 还是…
I don't know ‭if that makes it right or …
是对的
It does.
我当时不想错杀无辜
I didn't want to risk killing innocent people.
我本该只考虑我们的人
I should've just been worrying about our people.
其他人见鬼去吧
Hell with anyone else.
我们会继续抗争…
We'll keep fighting …
直到你准备好了
until you're ready.
我已经准备好了
I'm ready.
玛姬在外面设了警戒
Maggie's got lookouts out there.
八百米一个
Every half-mile,
相互传送信号 我知道
waiting to signal each other, I know.
没错 我也准备去
Yeah. I'm going, too.
去确保我们所有人都准备好了
To make sure we're all ready.
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
我们应该分头行动
We should split up.
要尽可能多覆盖一些范围
We're covering as much ground as we can.
好吧
All right.
我没事
I'm okay.
是吗
Yeah?
没事
Okay.
我会没事的
I'm gonna be okay.
达里尔…
Daryl…
谢谢你…
Thank you …
把他们安全带到这里
for getting them here.
你觉得他能缓过来吗
Think he'll come back from this?
你缓过来了吗
Have you come back?
我只是继续向前
I just keep going.
是啊
Yeah.
他们也会的
They will, too.
等我们了结这一切后会更难
It'll be harder after we finish this,
等一切都平静下来
when it's quiet.
只要尼根死了就不会更难
Not if Negan's dead.
至少对我而言不会
Not for me, at least.
对我而言也不会
Not for me, either.
你怎么看这个 小德
What do you make of this, D?
这个
This?
这个啊 我们这趟小旅行
This. Our little road trip?
了结一切的机会 没什么不对的
Opportunity to close. Nothing wrong with that.
拜托 小德
Come on, D.
说点真话
Let's rap here.
坦率一点
Let's get candid.
胡说几句
Let's get weird.
这里没别人 只有我俩
There's nobody here but us chickens.
两个头目之间的对话
Top guy to top guy,
我只想知道 按照你的分析
I just want to know if, in your analysis,
你真觉得在我们做了这么多 再加上
you believe these people are gonna cower and cave.
这次警告之后 这群人真的会退缩吗
after we deliver what amounts to yet another warning.
- 我可不是被请来动脑子的 - 非也
- Don't get paid to think. - ‭Not true.
非也
Not true.
我非常看重你的看法 德怀特
I value ‭your perspective, Dwight.
正反[烙铁]两面你都熟
You've been ‭on both sides of the iron.
如果你不打算回答的话
Well, ‭if you're not gonna answer,
那我来随便表达一下
let me extemporaneously express.
我怀疑这次行动
that I have my doubts this little maneuver.
是否真能达到我们想要的效果
is going to deliver the desired outcome.
你觉得我们应该换种做法吗
You think we should do it different?
不 不不
No. No, no.
完全不是
Not at all.
按照老大的计划进行
The big man's plan will get it done,
毫无疑问
no question.
我们把瑞克
We've thrown a lot at Rick,
寡妇 国王整得很惨
the widow, the King,
他们就是不放弃 一直反抗
and they just keep coming, keep fighting…
你看到了 我也看到了
you've seen it, I've seen it.
总之 我看到的都是同一个答案
Tallying it up, ‭I keep seeing the same answer…
他们不怕
they don't scare.
我不知道这是什么鬼东西
I don't know what the hell it is.
「如果你用食物或唱片填满箱子
"If you fill the crates with food or phonograph records,
我愿意换给你通向未来的钥匙「
I will gladly exchange them for a key to your future"?
上面列出了会面的地点
It lists coordinates for our meeting spot.
不是救世军
This isn't the Saviors.
他们宁愿轰开大门 出风头
They'd blow ‭through the gates, make a big show.
作风不符
This isn't that.
就算是他们 我也不会惊讶
I wouldn't put nothin' past them.
如果是陷阱 也太明显了
Well, if it is a trap, it's kind of obvious.
所以才更可能是陷阱
Which is ‭what could make it a trap.
万一…
What if…
万一真有人想帮我们呢
What if it's someone who actually wants to help?
如果有人想帮我们 我们错过了
If someone is trying to help us and we miss out,
也就错过了
we miss out.
可如果有人要害我们
If somebody's trying to kill us,
我们就死定了
we die.
多加小心就不会
Not if we're careful.
多加小心就别去
Being careful is staying here.
我去吧
I'll go.
- 我去看个究竟 - 你去我就去
- I'll see what's up. - You go, I go.
- 瑞克希望我们待在这 - 我知道
- Rick wants us here. - I know.
但上一次我们像这样碰运气
But the last time ‭we took a chance like this,
就改变了一切
it changed everything.
瑞克那时不同意我
Rick didn't agree with me then.
他现在或许也不会理解我
He may not understand me now.
他不会理解的
He won't.
但最终他会的
But eventually, he will.
他会的
He will.
耶稣和其他人一直在外搜刮
Jesus and the others have been scavenging,
可我们依然在挨饿
and we're still starving.
也许这人确实能帮到我们
Maybe this person does have something that can help.
那我也一起去
Then, I'm coming with you.
好
Okay.
我去拿些唱片 以备是真的
I'll grab records, case this is real.
你多带些弹夹 以备是假的
You get extra clips in case it isn't.
看到他们来了 请鸣笛
If you see 'em coming, hit your horn.
我们会接手
That'll start the handoff.
按计划来 不要掺和进去
Stick to the plan, don't engage.
怎么回事
The hell was that?
是尼根的车
That was Negan's car.
老天 没错
Jesus, it was.
该死
Damn it!
- 你看到了吗 - 嗯 有人狠狠撞了他
- You see it? - Yeah, someone pegged him…pegged him good.
看起来似乎只有一个人
Looked like just one guy, from what I could tell.
有人看到他朝哪边开了吗
Anyone see which way he went?
告诉他们安静点
Just tell them to pipe down!
冷静点
Stay icy.
也许还埋伏着更多人
May be more of them out there.
保持警戒 观察道路
Keep guards up, scan your lane.
可能有敌人
We could have company.
我们走
Let's go.
慢着
Whoa! Stand down.
没计划不能出击
No runnin' off without a plan.
尼根的车被另一辆车撞出主路了
Car hit Negan's, pushed him off the road.
他们朝那边去了 不可能走太远
They headed that way. Couldn't have gotten far.
那我们还等什么
Then, what are we waiting for?
只有一个开车的
It was just one driver.
尼根自己可以搞定
It's nothing Negan can't handle on his own.
但是为了以防万一
But just in case,
德怀特和我会去查看一下
Dwight and I'll go check it out.
- 好 我们可以当后援 - 不
- All right, ‭we can back you up and… - No.
这可能是分散我们兵力的阴谋
This might be a ploy to divide our forces,
我们不会让他们得逞的
and we're not gonna let that happen,
特别是我们这么接近成功的时候
not when we're so close to the master stroke.
我把货车转了向 确保没人从这边过来
I turned my truck to make sure no one comes in this way.
加里 我要你把那边也堵上
Gary, I want you to do the same down that end.
你来负责
You're in charge.
聚起大家 守好周围
Keep everyone in tight, create a perimeter,
轰掉任何试图靠近的东西
cut down anything that comes close.
我们去找大恩人吧
Shall we locate our benefactor?
刘易斯医药用品店
别进来
地下室[划掉]
进入之人 必死无疑
混蛋
Hey, prick.
你没子弹了
You are out of bullets.
上来啊
Come on up.
露西尔
Lucille!
你这个混蛋
Oh, you asshole.
好了
Okay.
我叫乔吉
My name is Georgie,
这两位是我的朋友 希尔达和米琪
and these are my friends, Hilda and Midge.
你们呢
And you are?
很可疑
Suspicious.
但你们很好奇
But curious enough.
想知道我会拿什么换食物和音乐
to see what I have to offer for food and music.
我的确希望这些唱片是音乐
I do hope the records are music.
我不接受只讲话的唱片
I don't accept spoken word.
你们能来这里
If you're out here,
证明你们能照顾好自己
you know you can take care of yourselves,
我喜欢这样
and I like that.
我无意与弱者分享这些
I don't care to share this with the weak.
很好
Good.
伊妮德
Enid.
我没枪
None for me.
把你的东西给我们
Give us what you have.
恐怕我不能这么做
I'm afraid I can't do that.
我是来用知识做交换的…
I come bearing knowledge to trade …
未来必要的知识
essential knowledge for the future,
主要在我头脑里
primarily in my head,
我希望我的头脑最好留在肩上
and, uh, I prefer ‭to keep that where it is.
你要用知识交换
You're trading knowledge.
没错
That's what I have.
我之前也和别人做过这样的交易
I've made the same offer before …
装满箱子 给你知识
fill the crates, get the knowledge …
就这么简单
simple as that.
不是什么把戏 只是公平的交易
It's not a trick, just a fair trade.
我保证
I promise you.
这是善意之举
It's an act of benevolence.
你为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
不然我还能怎么做
What else should I do?
罗西塔
Rosita.
那里的东西和交易无关
Uh, what's in there isn't part of the deal.
根本没有交易
There is no deal.
你找到了多少团体
How many communities have you found?
像你们这样的团体
Communities like yours?
不多
Not many at all.
很久没遇到过了
And not one for a very long time.
你们所拥有的非常特别 罕见
What you have is special, unusual.
亡者激发了我们最好和最坏的一面
The dead have brought out our best and worst,
近来最坏的一面盖过了最好的一面
and the worst has been outpacing the best lately,
但那不会持续太久
but that won't last forever.
不会的
It won't.
如果人们能再次互相相信
If, perhaps, people can believe in people again,
四箱补给的价值远不及
four crates of goods is worth far less.
一个可持续的未来
than a sustainable future.
以及一种相互的信任
and perhaps an exercise in trust.
我知道
I know …
现在「信任」听上去像是一个编出来的词
"Trust" Probably sounds like a made-up word now,
就像叽里咕噜
like flibberschticky.
或者故里呱啦
Or klompf.
或湿润
Or moisture.
别说了
Stop.
这不可能是真的
This isn't real.
没有人做你们所说的事还能活下来
No way anyone survives going around ‭doing what you say you're doing.
但我们活下来了
But we do.
也会继续活下去 因为我能看出
And we will, because I can divine.
你们是个很好的团队
that you are a fine group,
除了有点没礼貌
manners notwithstanding.
我们可以做个交易
We can make a deal.
不
No.
把这些人还有她们的车
These people and their van.
全部带回山顶寨
are coming with us back to Hilltop.
你还活着吗
You still alive?
老子是九命猫
I'm a goddamn cat.
来吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.
你在哪里
Where are you?
你的人去哪儿了
So, where's your people?
这会儿应该到了
They should be here by now.
我们没走多远
We didn't get that far.
他们会来的
Oh, they're coming.
你会死在这里
This I where you die…
被黑暗包围 无比孤独
…in the dark, all alone.
你到底有什么毛病 瑞克
What the hell is your problem, Rick?
我知道你现在经历着很多痛苦
I mean, I know you're working through some shit,
难以忍受的痛苦 我知道
the worst kind of shit, I know,
但你绝对是我这辈子见过的
but if you aren't the most stubborn know-it-all prick.
最固执最自负的人…
I've ever crossed dicks with…
你为什么不让我救你 瑞克
Why didn't you just let me save you, Rick?
我很擅长的
I'm good at it.
我救了救世堂 哨站
I saved everybody in the Sanctuary,
山顶寨 神之国所有人
the Outpost, Hilltop, Kingdom,
我救了他们所有人
I saved them all.
他们的孩子
Their kids…
能够安全地长大
…can grow up safe.
我们接管之后 他们没有任何伤亡
They didn't lose one after we took over.
那么多人
All those people.
在瑞克·格兰姆斯到来前都过得很好
were doing just fine before Rick Grimes!
噬肉者
你不只是辜负了你儿子
You've not only failed your boy,
你还辜负了你的子民 瑞克
you failed your people, Rick.
我想一想都觉得难受
Kind of makes me sick just thinking about it.
浪费了那么多潜能
All that wasted potential.
但你还有希望
But, see, ‭there is still hope for you.
我愿意跟你做个一次性的交易
A one-time deal that I will make.
为了纪念你霸气的儿子
in the memory of your bad-ass son,
向我真正佩服的人致敬
someone that I actually respected.
只要你劝山顶寨 神之国 亚历山大臣服
You get Hilltop, Kingdom, Alexandria to fall in line,
一切就恢复如常
and our arrangement is back in place,
我就原谅你 瑞克
and you are forgiven, Rick.
我会把提成从50%降到25%
I will lower my take from 50% to 25%,
仅仅25%而已
a lousy 25%.
但是你 你要来给我干活
But you, ‭you got to come work for me.
从清洁工做起 完全不算差
Janitorial to start, not bad at all.
你的子民 他们能活得像75%的国王
Your people, they get to live like 75% kings!
听好了 我摆在你面前的可是一份
Now, that is an epic freakin' Christmas-Hanukah-Kwanzaa gift.
肥得流油的节日大礼
all rolled up into one,
毕竟你一直以来给我找了那么多麻烦
considering what a thorn in my ass cheek you've all been.
你对简迪斯的人做了那样的事
Now, why would I trust any deal offered to me.
我为什么还要相信你的提议
after what you did to Jadis' people?
你他妈的在说什么
The hell are you talking about?
那些拾荒者
The Scavengers.
你杀了他们 一个不留
You killed them … all of them.
整个社区被血洗
A whole community just wiped out.
你就是那样「救人」的吗
Is that how you "Save" people?
那个混蛋
Son of a bitch.
依然只有我和你
Still just me and you…
虽然很多你的人肯定看到你走了
even though plenty of your people must've seen you go.
你看 就是在这种时刻
See … See, it's times like this,
你才会明白谁才是真正的朋友
you realize ‭who your true friends are.
没人会来救你的
No one's coming for you.
你肯定想过
You must've thought about it,
亲手干掉他
clipping him yourself.
你是指他霸占我老婆的时候吗
You mean when he took my wife?
或者烧焦我脸的时候吗
Or burned my face?
没有
No.
从没想过
Never thought about that.
一次都没有
Not once.
你没那样做是因为你选择了生存
But you didn't ‭because you chose to survive.
而不是纠结于过去的痛苦
instead of focusing on past discomforts.
你是个成年人
You are an adult.
你做了想要活下来必须做的事
You did what you had to to live.
但是我们的老大并没有这样做
And yet our leader is not doing the same.
如果我说了算
If it was my call…
就到此为止吧
we'd say enough.
我们会扩展领域 找新地盘
We'd branch out, we'd find new places,
建立新关系
we'd make new relationships.
我们会确保救世军活下来
We'd make sure the Saviors survive,
就像你的选择一样
as you chose to.
我们会从过去的痛苦中走出来
And we'd move on ‭from past discomforts as you…
就像你明智的选择一样
wisely chose to.
好了 我都说开了
Well, here I am,
蛋蛋敞开吹着冷风
my nuts blowin' in the breeze,
赤裸裸地站在这
naked as a jaybird.
你怎么说
What do you say?
就这么过去吗
Just move on?
就这么过去
Just move on.
可能是他的血
Could be his.
也可能是他带的那个桶里的血
Or the bucket he brought with him.
他可能在任何地方 活着或者死了
He could be anywhere, alive or dead.
半死不活
Somewhere in between.
他走开了
Just 'cause he walked away.
并不代表还活着
doesn't mean he's breathing.
我们可以继续找
We can keep looking,
也许找到他的时候还算是活着
maybe find him more alive than dead,
但然后呢
but then what?
我们要面对一个讨厌的时刻
We could face a distasteful moment.
或者我们可以走开
Or we could walk away.
回去找我们的人
Get back to our people.
让事情变得更好
and make things even better.
这是历史性的一刻 德怀特
This is a critical point in our history, Dwight.
这是我们以后可以告诉子孙的
This is something we could tell our grandkids about.
好答案
Good answer.
接力鸣笛响了
The handoff horn started up.
但是没有确认的袭击
but no confirmation hits.
救世军可能放慢速度了
Saviors could've slowed their roll.
随他们 我们会进一步拖住他们
Let 'em. ‭We'll slow 'em down more.
很好
That's good.
很快就天黑了
Be dark soon.
让大家准备好
Get people ready.
你知道该做什么
You know what to do.
我们应该抓紧交易
We should make the deal and let them go.
在救世军来之前放她们走
before the Saviors get here.
我不能让她走
I can't let her go,
不能让她们带着物资走
not with what they have.
我有很多张嘴需要喂
I got too many mouths to feed.
她们车里有很多食物
They have quite foods in that van.
这里的人很快就会挨饿的
People here could be starving soon.
玛姬说得对
Maggie's right.
我们夺走她们的物资
We take their stuff.
不然其他人也会夺走的
Otherwise, someone else will.
其他人会杀了她们
Someone else will kill them.
她们能活到现在已经是个奇迹了
It's a miracle ‭they're still alive, anyways.
救世军在路上了
The Saviors are on their way.
我们会战斗 会死一些自己人
We're gonna fight, and some of us will die,
所以何必在乎那些不自爱的人
so why should we give a shit about people who don't give a shit about themselves?
我是说 在外面像那样生存
I mean, out there, living like that?
我们夺走她们的东西并使用
We take their stuff, and we use it.
别再假装一切会好了
We stop pretending ‭that things just work out.
不会好的
They don't.
卡尔救了西迪克
Carl rescued Siddiq,
现在我们有了一个医生
and now we have doctor,
有了一个朋友
and we have a friend.
卡尔很勇敢
Carl was brave.
而他死了
And now he's dead.
退后
Step back.
事情不会自己好起来的
Things don't just work out.
没错
No.
不会的
No, they don't.
但我想他知道这点
But I think he knew that.
他没有放弃成为瑞克想让他成为的人
He didn't give up ‭on who Rick wanted him to be.
我们也不能放弃
And we can't.
成为卡尔想让我们成为的人
on who he wanted us to be.
我们不能放弃
We can't.
你的那一套
What you have…
永远不可能长久
oh, that was never gonna last.
迟早
Sooner or later,
你会遇到像我一样的人
you were gonna meet someone like me.
你救不了我
You can't save me.
或我的人 甚至是你的人
or my people or even yours.
你谁也救不了
You can't save anyone,
因为你谁也不在乎
because you don't care about anyone.
你利用人们 喂你吃
You use people to bring food…
陪你睡
to sleep with you…
保护你
to protect you.
你唯一在乎的
The only thing you care about…
是这球棒
is this bat.
而你连它都救不了
You can't even save that.
我来跟你谈个交易吧
I'll make you a deal.
我允许你和它吻别
I'll let you kiss her goodbye.
不准碰它
Don't you touch her!
过来拿啊
Come and get her.
该死 不
Shit, no!
别碰它
Get your hands off of her.
该死的疯子
Goddamn psychopath…
你会害死我们的
You're gonna kill us both.
只要你先死就行
Long as it's you first.
不是讲话吧
No spoken word?
我同意你的提议
I'm agreeing to your deal.
我们给你装满四箱 然后让你离开
We'll fill your four crates, then you can go.
你最好早走点
You're gonna want that to be sooner than later.
我接受
I accept.
但我要改变条件
But I'm changing the terms.
只要一箱
This one, no more.
此外
In addition,
你们可以拿走我一大部分的食物储备
you can have a sizeable portion of my food stores.
从这里的情况来看
From the looks of things around here,
你们比我们更需要
you need it far more than we do.
你要给我们食物吗
You're giving us food?
换什么
In exchange for what?
唱片和信任
Records and good faith.
澄清一下 这不是礼物 这是交易
To be clear, this isn't a gift, it's barter.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
也许不会很快 但我会回来的
Maybe not for a while, but I will,
到了那时 我期望看到伟大的成果
and by then, I expect great things.
这
Here…
是之前提到的通向未来的钥匙
is the aforementioned key to a future.
内有手写计划 包括风车
Inside, there are ‭handwritten plans for windmills,
水磨 筒仓 手绘原理图
watermills, silos, hand-drawn schematics,
细粮 木材 沟渠制作指南
guides to refining grain, creating lumber, aqueducts …
一部中世纪人类成就之书
a book ‭of medieval human achievement.
让我们用过去创造未来
so we may have a future from our past.
《通向未来的钥匙》
早期文明至今的机械 技术
任务 劳作 解决方法指南
一条从过去走向更先进未来的道路
是的 我知道 原版在我脑海中
Yes, I know, ‭the originals are in my head,
但我做了拷贝
but I made photocopies.
不过自从做好之后
Still, it's been an evolving document.
一直在改动更新
since the copy shop.
谢谢你
Thank you.
建好这地方
Build this place up.
下次我回来时 要把其他几箱装满
I want those other crates filled when I get back …
给希尔达的奶酪 给米琪的腌菜
cheeses for Hilda, pickles for Midge.
我们会尽力的
We'll see what we can do.
你们会的
You will.
我杀了娜塔尼亚
I killed Natania.
她在外面试图杀死碰见的任何人
She was out there trying to kill anyone she came across,
而我们碰见了她
and we came across her.
我杀了她 所以我还活着
So I killed her, and I'm alive,
卡尔救了某人 所以他死了
and Carl saved someone, and he's dead.
我们该怎么做啊
How the hell ‭are we supposed to do this?
难道要停止战斗吗
Are we supposed to just stop fighting?
我觉得卡尔不想让我们停止为了未来而战
I don't think Carl wanted us to stop fighting for our future.
但我觉得他想告诉我们 要想有未来
But I think he was telling us that, to get to our future,
光靠战斗是不够的
it's gonna take ‭more than just fighting.
救世军正在来这里的路上
The Saviors are coming right now.
我们会与他们战斗
And we're gonna fight them.
但未来一定不只如此
But there's gotta be something after.
他没和他们在一起
He's not with them.
尼根呢
Where's Negan?
不见了
Gone.
你们找不到他吗
You couldn't find him?
只有血
Just blood.
现在怎么办
Now what, hmm?
我们该做什么
What are we supposed to do now?
你是谁
Who are you?
尼根
Negan.
谁
Who?!
尼根
Negan!
我是尼根
I am Negan!
你他妈当然是
Damn right you are!
我们都是
We all are!
老大在不在无所谓
Don't matter ‭if the big man ain't here.
我们依然是尼根
We're still Negan.
我们不知道他是不是真死了
We don't know if he's "Gone" Gone.
他依然很有可能回来
He could very well be back.
我们的计划 尼根的计划
Our plan … Negan's plan …
是去山顶寨
was to go on to Hilltop.
在那些人的心中埋下恐惧
and put the fear of God in these people.
让他们终于任我们摆布
so that, finally, once and for all, they get with the program.
但在刚发生过的事之后
But after what just happened,
在他们那样对尼根之后
what they did to Negan,
我认为他们无法领会我们的意思
that tells me that what we need from them is beyond them.
是时候接受这点了
It's time we come to accept that.
接受以后 一切都豁然开朗
And once we do, it'll become crystal clear.
现在只有一件事可做
there's only one thing left for us to do.
我们必须清洗他们
We must expunge them.
我们必须抹消他们
We must redact them!
我们要擦掉他们这个错误
They are a mistake that we shall now erase.
我们要向前看
We are moving on.
为了尼根
For Negan!
好吗
Yes?
为了尼根
For Negan!
该死
Well, shit.
闭嘴
Shut up.